[sirens wailing in distance]
- Shit. shit. shit.
- [horn honks]
- [Cary] Whoa.
- [tires squeal]
[sirens wailing]
[tires screech]
[indistinct chattering]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Excuse me. sir. You have to help me.
My grandmother. she's hurt.
- Try to stay calm.
- No. I can't lose her.
We're gonna take care of your grandmother.
but we need to get you on a stretcher too.
I'm fine. I just...
[stammers] I need to be with her.
You're still in shock.
You could have serious injuries.
Sir. please let me go with her.
If she dies. and I'm not with her...
Please.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
[indistinct announcement]
[paramedic] Seventy-one year old woman.
multiple injuries.
Possible head trauma. collapsed lung.
Blood pressure around 50.
We got it up to 80 with adrenaline.
[paramedic 2] It's okay.
Can you squeeze my hand?
Can you try to squeeze it?
[panting]
Hey! Excuse me. You're the granddaughter?
Uh. what? Um. yes.
And what's her name?
- [Lucky] Ruth Turner.
- And you are?
- Amanda... [breathes shakily] ...Turner.
- Okay.
Is she on any current medications?
[stammers] I'm not sure.
[distorted] Can you help
with her medical history?
- No. I... No.
- [echoing] Any preexisting conditions?
I was just visiting her for the week.
okay? I don't--
Is she gonna be okay?
We'll do our best to save her.
Okay.
[groans]
- Hey. we need to get you checked out too.
- No. I'm fine.
- You're in shock.
- I'm fine. [breathing shakily]
Is there a drinking fountain?
I just really need some water.
[echoing] I'll get you a cup.
Stay right there. I'll be right back.
[breathing shakily]
No!
- Faster. Lucky. Come on.
- I'm trying.
Are you okay?
[theme song playing]
[rhythmic beeping]
- [beeping continues]
- [gasps]
[nurse] Feeling better?
Um...
- How long have I been here?
- Not long.
- What happened?
- You fainted.
It's pretty common
in situations like yours.
You were running on adrenaline.
Ruth is in surgery.
Who?
Your grandmother.
She's still critical.
but they're doing everything they can.
You rest. okay?
- [groans]
- [beeping]
[groaning]
Oh. my God. Billie.
[sighs]
Hey. She's going to be okay.
- [door opens]
- [gasps]
[sobbing]
Here.
I'm fine.
You don't look fine.
[sighs]
[sniffles] Someone I love might die.
And the last thing I said to her was.
"I hate you."
I used to tell my dad
I hated him all the time.
Didn't mean it.
I would've done anything for him.
and I think he knew that.
Maybe that's what I hated.
I don't know what to do.
Go in there and make sure she knows
you didn't mean it.
- [indistinct radio chatter]
- [breathes shakily]
[sniffles]
[grunts]
Oh. Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm fine. I just. uh. need a room
for the night. Whatever's cheapest.
Of course. ID. please.
[softly] Yeah.
[knocks on door]
Hello. I'm Peter Kershaw. Billie's boss.
Yeah. I'm Alison. We've met before.
Uh. uh...
How's. uh... How's she doing?
She has a cranial contusion.
They're gonna keep her a couple of days
for observation.
You catch the people she was after?
One of them was dead on arrival.
We're still looking for the other one.
Who? Who's dead?
[Kershaw] Cary Masterson. Gunshot wound.
- And Lucky?
- We don't have her.
[inhales] Then. what are you doing here?
Just making sure
you didn't get yourself killed.
[inhales sharply] Let me have some water.
[breathes shakily]
I'm sure she's not far. [breathes shakily]
She's probably hurt somewhere.
You need to find her while she's local.
Yeah. And you need to stop obsessing
and get some rest.
Amen.
- Where's Gates?
- [Kershaw] Doing his job.
That's your last question. all right?
I came here to check on you.
not rile you up.
All right? I'll let you know
when we have any updates.
[footsteps approaching]
[Dutch] Here you go.
[sighs. sniffles]
I. uh... I want him cremated.
And we'll do a memorial service
as soon as possible.
I don't want him lying alone
in some cold. dark morgue.
I'll take care of it.
I don't know who his friends are.
Or even if he has any.
I guess it will be my people.
I suppose I don't have many
of those left either.
More than you think.
Wayne should be told.
I'll call his people.
You think he'll come?
Hmm.
Let's put the boy to rest. Set him free.
Everything else is. um...
Well. it's just secondary.
Yeah. you're right.
I'm gonna give you some space.
You can sit down. Please.
Go ahead. you can call them now.
See what Wayne has to say.
[young Lucky gasps]
[inhales sharply]
[indistinct chattering on TV]
[young Lucky] It's nothing.
I don't know what I'm trying to say.
[John] I think you do.
Are we bad people?
What makes you think that?
Well. I'm pretty sure
we're not good people.
Given it a lot of thought. huh?
What's our source of heat? On Earth.
The sun.
What's our source of cold?
Antarctica?
There is no source of cold.
Cold is just the absence of heat.
So it just becomes a question
of how far you are from the sun.
Mmm. it's a question of degree.
So you're saying there is no evil?
Just how far you are from good?
Good and evil are man-made concepts.
And like everything else man-made.
they're highly imperfect.
Do you think a lion wastes one second
wondering whether it's good or bad
to kill an antelope?
He's doing what he has to to survive.
Yeah. but we're not animals.
Only because we say we're not.
[dark music playing]
[sniffs]
[sniffling]
[bartender] What can I get you?
Your cheapest bourbon. please.
and a sugar cube.
It's on the house.
Thank you.
[patron] Isn't that some shit?
[sighs] Some people have all the luck.
[sighs] You'll have to excuse me.
You caught me in a bad mood.
It's all right.
[sighs] My flight home got canceled.
I've had a pretty shitty day myself. so...
Well then. to our bad luck.
- And fuck that guy.
- [chuckles] Yeah.
Fuck that guy.
Now I'm missing my daughter's birthday
because of that flight.
I just don't wanna fuck her up. you know?
The fact that you're worried about that
probably means that
you have nothing to worry about.
So. what happened to you?
[scoffs]
The. um. bellman gave me
the wrong suitcase.
Which means that somebody's
probably out there with mine.
They promised me they're gonna
track it down. but until then. I'm...
You're just wearing
some stranger's clothes?
No. [chuckles]
No. these are my husband's clothes.
actually. He. uh...
He died today.
I'm wearing them because
mine are covered in blood.
We were in a car wreck. and now he's dead.
And I'm here talking to you.
[chuckles]
Sorry. you'll have to. uh. forgive me.
I'm not very used to being honest.
Uh. any other day. I would've
just continued the bullshit suitcase story
and used your guilt over your daughter
to manipulate you into paying for my room
and giving me some extra money...
And you know what's really shitty
about all of that?
Is that I wouldn't even
have to ask you for it.
You would insist. [chuckles]
Because I know the perfect words to use
for a guy who worries
about his little girl.
But that's not what you're doing?
[chuckles. sniffles] No.
Why not?
Because I'm really tired
of being this way.
[sniffles]
And. um... [sniffles]
...today I really need to believe
that I'm not a totally bad person. [cries]
[sobbing]
[chuckles]
Well. someone wise once told me.
"The fact that you're worried about it
probably means
you don't have to worry about it."
[laughs]
She wasn't very wise.
[sighs]
The car wreck. your husband.
That's true?
We were fighting. [chuckles. sighs]
And I really regret what I said.
Those don't have to be your last words.
Okay. Yoda.
[both chuckling]
- Thanks.
- Want another drink?
- Yeah. [chuckles] Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Can we get another one. please?
- [both chuckling]
[gunshot]
- [breathes sharply]
- [gunshot]
Oh. fuck. Priscilla.
Priscilla!
Priscilla.
[gunshots]
[sighs]
Oh. it feels so good. [sighs]
- [hammer cocks]
- [sighs]
Oh.
[breathes sharply]
[yelling]
[yells]
[sighs]
[inhales deeply]
[sniffles]
[grunts]
[sighs] Did I kill him. Dutch?
Did I do this?
- Of course not.
- No. Did I put him in that car?
If he would have done what you told him
to do. he'd... he'd be alive right now.
Yeah. but I... I put him in the life.
- I pushed him too hard.
- Come on.
No good's gonna come out
of talking like this.
Yes. but I did... I did though.
I mean. I could have...
I could have sent him away
to boarding school.
I could have done better by him.
I mean. it's normal in bad moments to...
to look back and do a...
a warped accounting of sorts. you know?
You might wanna find
somebody to blame even...
you know. even if it's ourselves.
That's just not how life works
in real-time. you know?
Life is just a million random choices
you make day after day. year after year.
and later on. you can. uh...
you know. manipulate them
to add up to anything you want.
- But... that doesn't make it true.
- Hmm.
Yeah. I don't know if you're being wise
or just full of shit.
- [laughing]
- It's a fine line. [laughs]
You. uh... You gonna be...
- shooting my piece any more there?
- [coughs]
Uh... not right now.
Okay. 'cause I gotta reload it.
Oh.
[exhales deeply]
[Gates] They're discharging you already?
More like she's discharging herself.
The doctor said I could go.
No. What he said is
he couldn't force you to stay.
Mmm. That's it. babe.
[Rand] I'll meet you two down in the car.
[breathes shakily]
- You need to take it easy.
- I'll try to do that. [grunts]
Will you?
We lost all our leads.
No Cary. No money. No Lucky.
We will find something again.
We always do.
Not by taking it easy.
- [car door closes]
- [engine starts]
[alarm chirps]
[engine starts]
[murmuring]
[sighs]
[breathes deeply]
[sniffles]
Priscilla. I am so sorry.
Priscilla.
Mmm...
So. uh. did he even bother
to send flowers?
Flowers wouldn't have made a difference.
[sighs]
Uh. wh-where are you going?
I need to be alone.
[Dutch] You have a lot of people here.
That's why I'm leaving.
[sighs]
[Dutch] Priscilla.
There's someone here to see you.
I'll leave you two be.
You got some nerve showing up here.
He was my husband.
Yeah. well.
he was always a bit too easily led.
Yeah. Till he wasn't.
Until he wasn't.
Why are you here. Lucky?
The money is gone.
What do you mean "gone"?
Cary was the only person
who knew where it was.
Uh-huh. And he didn't tell you.
Never got the chance.
You expect me to believe that?
You're gonna believe
whatever you want to believe.
Did you love him?
I did.
More than you will ever know.
How touching.
Priscilla. I can't keep running from you.
I gave you and John the opportunity
to rise above
his little nickel-and-dime schemes.
I saw real potential in you.
You fucked me.
Potential? We were pawns to you. Always.
Well. that's how you get in.
You pay your dues.
John never did a single damn thing
he didn't wanna do.
He knew the score.
Just like he knew what would happen to him
if he stole from me.
Okay. So. what now?
Well. now I'm gonna go upstairs
and grieve my son.
and you're gonna get the hell
off my beach.
And I suggest you figure out a way
to get your hands on that money.
because the next time I see you.
I won't be so goddamn cordial.
[sniffles. breathing deeply]
[sighs]
[panting]
[screams]
[grunting]
I hate you!
[breathing heavily]
[Cary] Apple. hamster. karma.
snow. holiday. sunset. pledge.
turkey. identity. purpose.
fossil. mushroom.
[breathing shakily]
- [Cary] Apple. hamster. karma...
- [gasps]
- ...snow. holiday. sunset. pledge. turkey...
- [punching keys]
...identity. purpose.
fossil. mushroom.
[gasps]
[breathing shakily]
Yes! [laughing]
[crying]
Okay...
You know they gave you muscle relaxers.
[sighs. groans]
Those things make me groggy.
- Maybe you need to be groggy.
- [sighs]
Hand me my laptop. please.
The doctor said no screen time.
You know I relax when I work.
And the doctor said minimize screen time.
I'm "minimizing."
[scoffs] Wow.
So now you're making me your enabler
and your drug dealer.
It's Advil. girl.
Thank you.
Oh. God.
Here. Sit next to me.
We can cowork-relax together. [sighs]
That's not a thing. That's weird.
- [chuckles] You calling me weird?
- You're weird. Yes.
- [kisses] Calling me weird.
- [chuckles]
What's more relaxing than going over
the details of a three-year-old case? Huh?
- What's more relaxing than that?
- I don't know. an edible.
That's not funny.
- And I'm gonna call the DEA on you.
- Okay.
[scoffs] Okay.
[Rand] An edible.
- Wait. wait. Go back.
- What?
Go back. That woman.
I think I saw her.
You saw this woman?
Yeah. at the hospital.
The day of the crash. In the bathroom.
What was she doing?
- I don't remember.
- Dana.
Dana. honey. I need you to remember.
What was she doing?
[sighs] Jesus. Mom. I don't know.
She was washing blood off her arm
or something.
Did she talk to you?
She talked about her dad.
Okay. What about him?
[sighs] Something about how she hated
that she would do anything for him.
- [breathes heavily]
- Mom?
- Where's my phone?
- Why?
- Wh... You're not supposed to be working.
- Where's my phone?
- Mom. you're not... [stutters]
- It's behind you.
- Mom.
- It's fine.
[exhales deeply]
[breathes shakily] Gates.
- [Dana scoffs]
- [Gates speaks indistinctly]
Yeah. I need you to call a favor in
to the DOJ...
[Gates] Yes. ma'am.
...but this stays between me. you.
and the wall.
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
You have an update for me?
Fuck you.
So. that's a no?
You know. I never asked you
for child support.
I never asked you to be a father.
I never asked anything of you.
You were well compensated.
[scoffs. inhales sharply]
[grunts]
- Get out. [breathes heavily] Get out.
- He was your son.
You couldn't show one shred
of human decency?
- Get out!
- Our son is dead.
He was already dead.
He was dead
the minute he stole that money.
Did you really think that I was just
gonna let him walk away from this?
And if you knew what was good for you.
you'd be out there.
and you'd be looking for it instead
of throwing your little fucking tantrums.
[grunts. exhales]
You've got nothing left
to threaten me with.
I'm not afraid of you anymore.
- [Priscilla grunting]
- [hammer cocks]
[shrieks]
You...
[breathes shakily]
...are still afraid.
[breathing shakily]
If you were anyone else in the world...
I'd have killed you a long time ago.
[breathes shakily]
Now. clean up this mess.
and then go get my money.
[breathes heavily]
[John panting]
[guard] Armstrong. get up.
[exhales sharply] Five more.
Yeah. you're gonna wanna hurry
on this one.
[exhales sharply]
What's going on? [sniffles]
You're getting out.
[panting]
- What?
- You heard me.
On whose authority?
No idea. Warden told me to get you.
so that's what I'm doing.
Hey. You know most guys would kill
to be walking outta here. right?
Oh. yeah. Of course. [grunts]
I'm just wondering who's waiting for me
on the other side.
Well. there's only one way to find out.
[buzzer sounds]
[prisoners chattering indistinctly]
These are yours. Get dressed.
When's the last time
you saw a guy get out of here
with eight years left till parole?
Never.
That's what I figured.
I need you to review the items
and sign at the bottom.
Here's 200 bucks. courtesy of the State.
Count it. [sighs]
That's it?
Cab's waiting.
Where to?
Head west. I'll figure it out.
[phone ringing]
Dad?
I'm out.
- What?
- I was just discharged.
By who?
I can only think of two possibilities.
and neither one of them bode well for me.
It's Rand. She did it.
How can you be sure?
Because I know her. Dad.
She's using you to smoke me out.
Well. we shouldn't play into her hand.
Rand doesn't hold all the cards.
She just thinks she does.
If you say so.
Go to our place. The high one.
I'll meet you there.
[airplane passing overhead]
Hey. kid.
Hi. Daddy.
Ooh. Ow. careful.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
I've been better.
[sighs] You got a plan?
I have the money.
That's my girl.
[laughs]
So. what's the move?
Yeah. you're not gonna like it.
How about here?
Yeah. It seems about right.
[sucks teeth. sighs]
[sirens wailing]
You sure about this?
You're asking me this now?
["mq9" playing]
[tires screeching]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[Rand] What's up. John?
You're under arrest.
Took you long enough.
Okay.